Finding Aid for the James Arkatov Photographs PASC.0340.Coll-level-DAO
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Fine Artists, Series 3.
  - Witkin, Joel Peter, 1995; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Woelffer, Emerson, 1998; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Wonner, Paul, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Ojai, CA.
  - Wood, Beatrice, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    3 photographs. Photographs taken in Ojai, CA.
  - Wudle, Tom, 1991; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
  - Zajac, Jack, 1993; 8 x 10 b & w photographs (Box 7)
    2 photographs. Photographs taken in Santa Barbara, CA.
- Unidentified Cuban Artists, 1993; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Writers, Series 4.
  - Corwin, Norman, 1995; 8 x 10; b & w (Box 6, Folder 12)
    4 Photographs taken in Los Angeles, CA